Previously on
The Big Bang Theory...
Cohabitation with my girlfriend?
That's a great deal
to process.
(Sheldon:)Hmm?
It's only for five weeks.
Let me appeal
to the scientist in you.
Given the five-week
end date,
isn't it the perfect opportunity
to consider this an experiment
and collect data
on our compatibility?
Don't try luring me
in with sexy talk.
(Penny:)Okay.
Star Trek: The Original Series.
The Enterprise was
on a five-year mission
to explore new worlds.
Think of this
as your personal
five-week mission
to do the same.
Oh, you want to lure me in with
sexy talk, that's how you do it.
Okay, why don't you guys
stay across the hall
and we will
live here?
Very well. I'm on board.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
I accept this
five-week mission
to share a living space
with my girlfriend.
Oh. This is so exciting.
Well, now, don't be surprised
if, like Star Trek,
it's canceled in three.
(Penny:)Okay, I'm confused.
(Penny:)Which one is Mr. Robot?
(Leonard:)I'll give you a hint.
(Leonard:)We're watching
Daredevil.